A voice came crying from the wilderness edge
Prepare His way, His hour has nearly come
He walked south from the hills of Galilee
To stand where four thousand years of promise led
No sin to wash, no old life to bury
He stepped into the river anyway
The Father's voice heard above the water
This is my Son
I am well pleased with Him today
He could have had anything He desired
Instead He gave everything for those He loves
Into the water, into the wilderness
He was prepared in all things for us
Forty days with nothing but silence and hunger
A voice hissed doubt, tempting self service and pride
Are you who you think you are
Then prove it, take the shortcut
Make your greatness known, rule now
He didn't argue, didn't make it a debate
He reached for the word of God
As one does who knows his worth and truth
And will not move from it
Who came for sacrifice, not imitation of it
He could have had anything He desired
Instead He gave everything for those He loves
Into the water, into the wilderness
He was prepared in all things for us
He returned in the power of the Spirit
Not only surviving, strengthened
He stood in the room where He had grown up
And told them what they were looking at
This day, this scripture
Is fulfilled in your hearing
He could have had anything He desired
Instead He gave everything for those He loves
Into the water, into the wilderness
He was prepared in all things for us
For us, for us